

EDUCATION

UC San Diego Extension
UX Design Certificate Program
2018 - 2019

UC Santa Barbara B.S. Biological Sciences 2012 - 2014

SKILLS

Sketch

Illustrator

Photoshop

InDesign

InVision

HTML/CSS

User Research

Wireframes

Iterative Design

Prototyping

Petting Cats

PROFILE

I'm a designer in the truest sense of the word. With over six years of combined experience in graphic/visual/UX design, I've been responsible for strengthening visual identities and building products with a user-first mentality. I advocate for simple but powerful designs.

EXPERIENCE

Visual Designer | Engagio San Mateo, CA

Jan. 2018 - Present

- Own website design to bring user-friendliness and simplicity
- Create wireframes, userflows, and personas to communicate ideas
- Design print material for marketing collateral and graphics for ads

Visual Designer | SF Hep B Free San Francisco, CA

Dec. 2017 - Present

- Provide print and digital designs for ads, posters, infographics, brochures and other things for Asian health nonprofit
- Help organization conceptualize ideas to communicate to health professionals about hepatitis B

UX/Product Designer | Controlco

Sep. 2016 - Oct. 2017

Pleasant Hill, CA

- Created IoT applications using HTML/CSS, Niagara 4 and DGLux5
- Provided wireframes and user storyboards to communicate design
- Brought new design initiatives and UX best practices to products

Freelance Designer

2012 - Present

• Design everything from digital illustrations, logos, banners, t-shirts, icons, and UI assets for web and mobile